Welcome to this section.
-: Bienvenido a esta seccin.
In this section we're going to look
En esta seccin vamos
at one of the most complicated topics in Python.
a ver uno de los temas ms complicados en Python.
So complicated in fact that I have not seen another course
Tan complicado, de hecho, que no he visto otro curso
that covers this topic.
que cubra este tema.
The topic is asynchronous development with Python
El tema es el desarrollo asincrnico con Python
and that means doing multiple things at once essentially.
y eso significa hacer muchas cosas a la vez esencialmente.
I'll let you know that you cannot run two things at once
Te dejar saber que no puedes ejecutar dos cosas a
in Python, but throughout this section we're going to look
la vez en Python, pero a lo largo
at how you can pretend like you do
de esta seccin vamos a ver cmo puedes fingir que
and how that can speed up your programmes.
lo haces y cmo eso puede acelerar tus programas.
Asynchronous development, as I said, is a complicated topic,
El desarrollo asncrono, como dije, es un tema
so throughout this section,
complicado, por lo que
I'm also going to be referring you to a number
a lo largo de esta seccin,
of other videos and other sources
tambin los referir a otros videos y
from some of Python's developers themselves
otras fuentes de algunos desarrolladores de Python que
who have worked on making Python a language
han trabajado para hacer de Python un lenguaje
that supports asynchronous development.
que admite el desarrollo asincrnico.
Again, bare with me.
De nuevo, desnudo conmigo.
If you have any questions throughout the entire section,
Si tiene alguna pregunta en toda la seccin,
ask away in the course Q and A,
pregunte en el curso Q y A,
and if anything confuses you,
y si algo lo confunde,
and we will be glad to help you out.
A, y estaremos encantados de ayudarlo.
I'll see you on the next video.
Te ver en el prximo video.